Tony Antony

ABOUT ME

Engineer

Since 2018

A driven engineer with broad experience in the industry, with a successful track record in solving diverse Engineering problems, confident in bringing a fresh perspective to your organization and its various business problems.

EXPERIENCE

Vualapp

Aug 2022 - April 2023 | Full-stack Developer

- Collaborated with a 2 person founding engineering team to automate the invoice aggregation procedure, making the platform a viable solution for accounting customers.
- Conducted thorough research into current industry developments (HN) and successfully contributed to the overall optimization of production.
- Effectively contributed to implementing modularity, scalability, and bug fixes for the existing codebase.
- Implemented an event-based microservice on serverless compute, specifically AWS Lambda.
- > Facilitated the successful migration of the product between AWS accounts by transferring configurations, instances, security groups, and identity and access management, while documenting the entire procedure.
- Contributed to all aspects of product building, including development, testing, and documentation.
- > Primary stacks used include Vue, AWS (Lambda), and Supabase, with Gitlab for version control and CI/CD.
- Helped the organization build a sustainable browser automation solution using Puppeteer/Playwright.
- Created Postgres functions for database management using Chatgpt prompting, ensuring reliability and accuracy, and deployed them in production, eliminating the need to create a microservice for the same requirement.

Freelance

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022 | Web Developer

- Completed Modern React with Redux course from udemy. Learned basics of web development with the help of Youtube and stackoverflow, got myself familiarized with Git and vscode.
- Successfully developed more than eight react projects with real-life applications.

SIBCA Electronics Equipment

April 2019 - June 2021 Technichal Service Engineer

- > Programmed, commissioned, and serviced Extra Low Voltage systems and Central Battery systems.
- Communicated with clients, delivered services, and planned resources.
- > Delivered technical project documentation.
- Demonstrated hands-on experience in operating and troubleshooting various scalable electronic systems

EDUCATION

TKM College of Engineering

2014 – 2018 | Bachelor of Technology in Electronics and Communication

NAAC Accredited Govt-Aided Engineering college under Kerala University

SKILLS

JavaScript

Expert Level

Completed 69-hour beginner to Expert JavaScript course from udemy. Working on DSA

ES6	Node	React	Redux		Vue			
Object Oriented Programming boolean logic								
inheritance Asynchronous JavaScript								

Other

Prompting	HTML	CSS	Git	AWS		Linux serve	
Lambda	Lambda Hosting		Shell scripting		Sup		
Postgres	I/CD on Gitlab			LI	EC2	S3	
Cloudflare	y Groups IAM			VPO	2		
Cloudwatch	h autor	automation		Puppeteer		Playwright	
Fiddler	REST API						

CONTACT

https://tonyantony.xyz https://github.com/tonyantony300 lndiranagar, Banglore tonyantony300@gmail.com (+91) 944 710 999 1